<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="mainActivityTitle">Movie search</string>
    <string name="appName">Movie search</string>
    <string name="ocean11ru">Ocean\'s 11</string>
    <string name="ocean12ru">Ocean\'s 12</string>
    <string name="buttonDetails">Details</string>
    <string name="detailsButton">Details</string>
    <string name="inviteFriendButton">Invite friend</string>
    <string name="invitationTitle">Send email!</string>
    <string name="invitationSubject">Look at this wonderful app!</string>
    <string name="sendButtonName">Send!</string>
    <string name="invitationText">It searches movies! (Will be I guess)</string>
    <string name="ocean11_descr">A rag-tag group of con artists and ex-cons team up for the heist to end all heists in this high-profile remake of the 1960 Rat Pack favorite. As with its predecessor, Ocean\'s Eleven opens with its titular hero Danny Ocean (George Clooney stepping into the Frank Sinatra role) eager for a new challenge. The similarities to the original end there, as Ocean conspires with his old pal Rusty Ryan (Brad Pitt) to rob 150 million dollars from an underground vault that serves three of Las Vegas\' biggest casinos. Between the two of them, they recruit nine other men, each with his own criminal specialty, to assist in the mission: moneyman Reuben Tishkoff (Elliot Gould), card dealer Frank (Bernie Mac), pickpocket Linus (Matt Damon), aging con artist Saul (Carl Reiner), British explosives pro Basher (Don Cheadle), techie Dell (Eddie Jemison), rude-boy brothers Virgil (Casey Affleck) and Turk (Scott Caan), and professional acrobat Yen (Shaobo Qin). What Ocean doesn\'t tell the group is that there\'s another reason he\'s coordinating the heist: the three casinos they\'re robbing are all owned by ruthless gambling mogul Terry Benedict (Andy Garcia), who just happens to be married to Ocean\'s former love Tess (Julia Roberts).</string>
    <string name="ocean12_descr">After pulling off the heist of their lives, Danny Ocean and his pals unexpectedly find themselves back in harness in this sequel to 2001\'s blockbuster hit Ocean\'s Eleven. After robbing a cool $160 million from the Bellaggio Hotel Casino and winning back his former wife, Tess (Julia Roberts), from Bellagio owner Terry Benedict (Andy Garcia), Danny Ocean (George Clooney) is living quietly on the lam in Connecticut when he\'s unexpectedly approached by Benedict. It seems Benedict has tracked down Danny and the ten men who helped him pull off the seemingly impossible robbery, and Benedict offers them a proposal — if they can repay the $160 million in two weeks, he won\'t have them killed. As it turns out, both Danny and his best friend, Rusty Ryan (Brad Pitt), haven\'t been doing so well in terms of money management and could use some cash, so they set out to plan a robbery to recover the loot, with the same crew helping out — Linus Caldwell (Matt Damon), Frank Catton (Bernie Mac), Basher Tarr (Don Cheadle), Saul Bloom (Carl Reiner), Reuben Tishkoff (Elliott Gould), Livingston Dell (Eddie Jemison), Yen (Shaobo Qin), Virgil Malloy (Casey Affleck), and his brother Turk (Scott Caan). Danny and Rusty discover that an incredibly rare Fabergé egg is being displayed at a museum in Rome which would fetch the price they need, but they soon discover a notorious cat burglar, François Toulour (Vincent Cassel), is also after the egg, and it turns into a race to see who can claim it first. Adding to the intrigue is Isabel Lahiri (Catherine Zeta-Jones), a woman Rusty used to be involved with who is now a top agent with Interpol and is after both Toulour and Ocean\'s crew.</string>
</resources>